{
  "inputTimeWaitSecs": 120,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "2719 &minus; 8058",
      "answer": "-5339"
    },
    {
      "question": "3235 + -2560",
      "answer": "675"
    },
    {
      "question": "1302 + -9170",
      "answer": "-7868"
    },
    {
      "question": "-96 + -8805",
      "answer": "-8901"
    },
    {
      "question": "4537 &minus; 8343",
      "answer": "-3806"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4002 &minus; 4882",
      "answer": "-8884"
    },
    {
      "question": "5083 &minus; -9877",
      "answer": "14960"
    },
    {
      "question": "-8638 &minus; -310",
      "answer": "-8328"
    },
    {
      "question": "1411 &minus; -5045",
      "answer": "6456"
    },
    {
      "question": "-872 + -3646",
      "answer": "-4518"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2148 + 7137",
      "answer": "4989"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9496 + 8328",
      "answer": "-1168"
    },
    {
      "question": "-354 + -2043",
      "answer": "-2397"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7204 + -5819",
      "answer": "-13023"
    },
    {
      "question": "5065 + -1431",
      "answer": "3634"
    },
    {
      "question": "7217 &minus; -9010",
      "answer": "16227"
    },
    {
      "question": "-8725 + 1933",
      "answer": "-6792"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2211 &minus; -8746",
      "answer": "6535"
    },
    {
      "question": "5373 + -2357",
      "answer": "3016"
    },
    {
      "question": "8161 + 6426",
      "answer": "14587"
    },
    {
      "question": "1686 &minus; -6245",
      "answer": "7931"
    },
    {
      "question": "473 + 3979",
      "answer": "4452"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4009 + 8979",
      "answer": "4970"
    },
    {
      "question": "1691 &minus; 9546",
      "answer": "-7855"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4615 + 5536",
      "answer": "921"
    },
    {
      "question": "993 + -5954",
      "answer": "-4961"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3626 + 228",
      "answer": "-3398"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6675 + 8381",
      "answer": "1706"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9708 + 9792",
      "answer": "84"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9276 + 658",
      "answer": "-8618"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9911 + 7705",
      "answer": "-2206"
    },
    {
      "question": "-205 + 8941",
      "answer": "8736"
    },
    {
      "question": "8905 + 3237",
      "answer": "12142"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6940 + 1858",
      "answer": "-5082"
    },
    {
      "question": "394 + -8971",
      "answer": "-8577"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2481 &minus; -8512",
      "answer": "6031"
    },
    {
      "question": "-8689 &minus; -3281",
      "answer": "-5408"
    },
    {
      "question": "9535 &minus; 236",
      "answer": "9299"
    },
    {
      "question": "9091 + 2912",
      "answer": "12003"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3507 + 5765",
      "answer": "2258"
    },
    {
      "question": "-5385 &minus; -6217",
      "answer": "832"
    },
    {
      "question": "3400 &minus; -7000",
      "answer": "10400"
    },
    {
      "question": "2802 + 4294",
      "answer": "7096"
    },
    {
      "question": "2035 &minus; 7006",
      "answer": "-4971"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4275 &minus; 92",
      "answer": "-4367"
    },
    {
      "question": "2994 + 5365",
      "answer": "8359"
    },
    {
      "question": "5006 + -2348",
      "answer": "2658"
    },
    {
      "question": "2286 + 2851",
      "answer": "5137"
    },
    {
      "question": "-5601 + -903",
      "answer": "-6504"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2247 + -4017",
      "answer": "-6264"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4720 + -2000",
      "answer": "-6720"
    },
    {
      "question": "4453 + -1295",
      "answer": "3158"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4162 + -7990",
      "answer": "-12152"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4709 &minus; 1393",
      "answer": "-6102"
    },
    {
      "question": "-1190 + 8421",
      "answer": "7231"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2481 + -3714",
      "answer": "-6195"
    },
    {
      "question": "1999 + 4891",
      "answer": "6890"
    },
    {
      "question": "2730 &minus; 3378",
      "answer": "-648"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4913 &minus; 1475",
      "answer": "-6388"
    },
    {
      "question": "9795 + -8020",
      "answer": "1775"
    },
    {
      "question": "-8677 + -4666",
      "answer": "-13343"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9442 &minus; 4821",
      "answer": "-14263"
    },
    {
      "question": "-5072 + -6770",
      "answer": "-11842"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3102 + 6293",
      "answer": "3191"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7914 + -6002",
      "answer": "-13916"
    },
    {
      "question": "7000 &minus; 19",
      "answer": "6981"
    },
    {
      "question": "7835 + 4447",
      "answer": "12282"
    },
    {
      "question": "7704 &minus; -9801",
      "answer": "17505"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2211 + 5696",
      "answer": "3485"
    },
    {
      "question": "3042 &minus; -5170",
      "answer": "8212"
    },
    {
      "question": "-5711 + 2799",
      "answer": "-2912"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7769 + -842",
      "answer": "-8611"
    },
    {
      "question": "744 &minus; -9905",
      "answer": "10649"
    },
    {
      "question": "9857 + 3602",
      "answer": "13459"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7375 + -9312",
      "answer": "-16687"
    },
    {
      "question": "-8898 &minus; 5168",
      "answer": "-14066"
    },
    {
      "question": "8615 &minus; 4247",
      "answer": "4368"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4712 &minus; -4319",
      "answer": "-393"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6203 + -7690",
      "answer": "-13893"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4669 + -9762",
      "answer": "-14431"
    },
    {
      "question": "-9183 &minus; -9707",
      "answer": "524"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7316 &minus; -3089",
      "answer": "-4227"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2458 &minus; 5970",
      "answer": "-8428"
    },
    {
      "question": "9088 + -2235",
      "answer": "6853"
    },
    {
      "question": "6573 &minus; 6953",
      "answer": "-380"
    },
    {
      "question": "-8526 &minus; 1293",
      "answer": "-9819"
    },
    {
      "question": "6347 + 9483",
      "answer": "15830"
    },
    {
      "question": "8623 + -314",
      "answer": "8309"
    },
    {
      "question": "-5093 + 1620",
      "answer": "-3473"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6348 &minus; -9958",
      "answer": "3610"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7515 + -51",
      "answer": "-7566"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2677 + -9240",
      "answer": "-11917"
    },
    {
      "question": "-5358 &minus; -3040",
      "answer": "-2318"
    },
    {
      "question": "-1631 + -6408",
      "answer": "-8039"
    },
    {
      "question": "-1365 &minus; 7065",
      "answer": "-8430"
    },
    {
      "question": "9360 + 3432",
      "answer": "12792"
    },
    {
      "question": "3252 + -5241",
      "answer": "-1989"
    },
    {
      "question": "-1656 + 1754",
      "answer": "98"
    },
    {
      "question": "-7931 + 1194",
      "answer": "-6737"
    },
    {
      "question": "8454 + 1762",
      "answer": "10216"
    }
  ]
}
